<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infin8ty</title><link>https://infin8ty.net/</link><description>Recent content on Infin8ty</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://infin8ty.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NGO/NON-PROFIT COMMUNICATION</title><link>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/ngo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/ngo/</guid><description>Visuals concieved for non-profit initiatives working in the fields of climate change mobilization and refugee rights, based in Paris, France.</description></item><item><title>MOTION DESIGN/3D ANIMATION</title><link>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/motion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/motion/</guid><description>A compilation of 2D, 3D, and motion design work from between 2015-2019.</description></item><item><title>FRANCE-AMÉRIQUE / ALLIANCE FRANÇAISE OF NEW YORK</title><link>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/france-amerique/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/france-amerique/</guid><description>A selection of visuals conceived for communication purposes on behalf of the New York-based bilingual magazine France-Amérique, and their partner organization l’Alliance Française of New York.</description></item><item><title>LOGOS, ILLUSTRATIONS, CONCEPT ART</title><link>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/logos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://infin8ty.net/portfolio/logos/</guid><description>Logos, illustrations and concept art created for various businesses, print, and animated film projects.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://infin8ty.net/about.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://infin8ty.net/about.html</guid><description>Kelly Odette Dochy is French/Mexican-American from San Diego, California, currently residing in Paris, France. She works currently as a freelance content creator (graphic design, motion design, 3D, video editing), ESL teacher and video assistant to poet Alain Arias-Misson on a poetry video series, exhibited at the MuKHA (Antwerp, Belgium) and the Fondation Bonotto (Molvena, Italy).
In New York, she has been a graphic designer and illustrator for New York-based magazine France-Amérique.</description></item><item><title>Code of ethics</title><link>https://infin8ty.net/code.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://infin8ty.net/code.html</guid><description>Infin8ty is an initiative aiming to use art and media to catalyse awareness, and action on a diversity of societal issues, by rewriting old narratives, sharing a diversity of perspectives, and imagining alternate futures.
1
Infin8ty is an emerging project, collaborative and decentralized.
2
Encouraging diversity as an ingredient for resilience, Infin8ty wishes to work with individuals and organizations from diverse walks of life.
3
Quality and sustainability. “Less is more”.</description></item></channel></rss>